## JIN KUAN MOO

https://minahhh666.github.io/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/jin-kuan-moo/

### **Summary**

A UCD Computer Science Master proficient in Chinese Mandarin, English, and Malay. Full stack development experience in several languages as well as **Agile** methodology. Great networking (TCP/IP), distributed systems, database, OS, container, and cloud knowledge. Currently working as a freelance web designer and frontend developer. Previously worked as a manager, leading a team of 20 engaged in daily production. Volunteered in Code in Place hosted by Stanford University, delivering online Python lessons to a group of 15 students. Have more than 3 years of investing and trading experience with decent financial knowledge.

Email: jkmoo0412@hotmail.com

Mobile: 0892059402

#### **Education**

**University College Dublin** Dublin, Ireland MSc Computer Science; GPA:3.82 (First Class Honours) Sep 2022 – Dec 2023

**Cornell University** New York, United States Exchange Programme; GPA:3.87 (First Class Honours) Aug 2019 – Dec 2019

**University College Dublin** Dublin, Ireland BSc Food Science; GPA:3.77 (First Class Honours) Sep 2017 – Jun 2021

## **Experience**

**Freelancer** Dublin, Ireland Sep 2023 – Now

Web designer/Frontend developer

• Designing personal/commercial website for customers

Experience in WordPress, Domain & Email Hosting, HTML/CSS, JavaScript

**Stanford University** Dublin, Ireland Python Tutor Apr 2023 – Jun 2023

• Participating in Code in Place, an online introductory coding course

• Conducting weekly lessons for a cohort of 15 students

• Teaching topics including Python, Animations, Console Programming, Graphic Programming etc.

**Krispy Kreme** Kildare, Ireland Manufacturing Manager Sep 2021 – Jun 2022

- Managing a 20-member team for daily production operations
- Ensuring adherence to safety protocols, HACCP principles, and legal regulations
- Maintaining accurate inventory control, yield records, and traceability documents

### **Projects**

# **Afterparty (Backend Developer)**

an event impact analysis tool which provides insights into how the busyness of urban areas are impacted by largescale event.

- Utilized React.js, Mapbox GL.js, and Figma for the frontend development
- Implemented the backend with Node.js, Express.js, Flask, and Apache
- Developed prediction models using Random Forest and XGBoost

### **Dublin Bikes (Full-Stack Developer)**

a web application providing real-time information and journey planning for bike-sharing services.

- Utilized Vanilla JS, HTML, CSS, and Google Maps API for frontend development
- Implemented the backend with Flask, MySQL, AWS EC2, AWS RDS, Gunicorn, Nginx
- Developed prediction models using Linear Regression

### **Asteroids (Frontend Developer)**

a classic arcade video game which player controls a spaceship in an asteroid field to destroy incoming asteroids.

- Developed using Java
- Used JavaFX as the GUI framework

## **Technical Skills**

- Programming languages: Python, JavaScript, Java, Ruby, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, Spring Boot, Bash, Astra
- Frameworks: React.js, Flask, Express.js, JavaFX, Pygame
- Database: MySQL, AWS RDS, NoSQL, MongoDB
- OS: Linux, Windows
- Tools: Jupyter Notebook , Microsoft Office, WordPress
- DevOps: Jenkins, GitHub, Unit Testing, Apache Maven
- Cloud: AWS, GCP, Docker, Kubernetes
- Distributed Systems: MapReduce, Hadoop, Spark, Rest, RMI, Middleware, Web Services
- Machine Learning: Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, Random Forest, XGBoost, KNN, Scikit-learn
- Others: Data Structures and Algorithms, Networking (TCP/IP), OOP, CI/CD

### **Honours**

- UCD Global Southeast Excellent Scholarship
- UCD Food Science Scholarship
- Kepak Best in Class Award